zettai.net 2009-06-22

# Privacy Policy

Zettai Ltd ("Zettai") is committed to protecting your privacy, and complies with the Data Protection Act 1998. Your personal details are not held or used without your permission. 

Zettai reserves the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time, without notice, and you should check back to this policy regularly to be informed of any changes. 

**Search User Information**

It is not necessary to provide Zettai with personal information in order to use the Zettai.net service as a search user. Data may be gathered about use of the Zettai.net in order to enhance your experience using cookies. Further data may also be collected with your permission using questionnaires, feedback forms, competition entries or similar or you may be invited to register in order to receive updates tailored to your interests. 

Queries and comments received via our websites, via email and by telephone are also monitored in order to enhance the Zettai customer service and the search user experience of the Zettai.net service. 

Information gathered may be used to report on usage of the Zettai.net service and such reports will be generic in nature and will not report on individual or personal details or behaviour. 

**Zettai's use of Cookies**

A cookie is a small data file that certain Websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. 

Zettai Directories does not store passwords or any personal information about you. The site may use cookies to identify you anonymously in its database and to track the pages you visit on the site. Cookies may also enable you to enter sections of the Website without having to supply certain information each time, and to visit member-restricted areas of the sites. 

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. 

**Information Storage and Security**

Zettai uses all reasonable endeavours to ensure the security of systems on which personal data is stored and may be processed. 

The Zettai.net service provides links to third party websites for which Zettai has no responsibility. Zettai does not share personal data with these websites, except where they may be selected partners of Zettai. Any information which you provide to these websites will be subject to the privacy policies of the individual websites.
